Conservative Party Archive: Constituency Correspondence CPA CCO 1
Conservative Party Archive
- Constituency files, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8
  - Area N - Scotland, Apr 1950-Aug 1951
    - Lanarkshire, North, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/591; 1.0 file
    - Lanarkshire, Rutherglen, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/592; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh Central, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/593; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh East, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/594; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh Leith, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/595; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh North, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/596; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh Pentlands, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/597; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh South, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/598; 1.0 file
    - Edinburgh West, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/599; 1.0 file
    - Midlothian and Peebles, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/600; 1.0 file
    - Moray and Nairnshire, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/601; 1.0 file
    - Orkney and Zetland, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/602; 1.0 file
    - Perthshire and Kinross-shire, Kinross and West Perthshire, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/603; 1.0 file
    - Perthshire and Kinross-shire, Perth and East Perthshire, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/604; 1.0 file
    - Renfrewshire and Greenock, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/605; 1.0 file
    - Renfrewshire and Paisley, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/606; 1.0 file
    - Renfrewshire and East Renfrewshire, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/607; 1.0 file
    - Renfrewshire and West Renfrewshire, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/608; 1.0 file
    - Roxburgh and Selkirk, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/609; 1.0 file
    - Stirling and Falkirk Burghs, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/610; 1.0 file
    - Stirlingshire and Clackmannan, Clackmannan and East Stirlingshire, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/611; 1.0 file
    - Stirlingshire and Clackmannan, West Stirlingshire, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/612; 1.0 file
    - West Lothian, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/613; 1.0 file
    - [Vacant], Apr 1950-Aug 1951; [CCO 1/8/614]
  - Area O - Northern Ireland, Apr 1950-Aug 1951
    CCO 1/8/615-25
    - Northern Ireland, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/615/625; 1.0 file
    - [Vacant], Apr 1950-Aug 1951; [CCO 1/8/615-16]
    - Belfast West By-Election, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/617; 1.0 file
    - [Vacant], Apr 1950-Aug 1951; [CCO 1/8/618-23]
    - Londonderry By-Election, Apr 1950-Aug 1951; CCO 1/8/624; 1.0 file
    - [Vacant], Apr 1950-Aug 1951; [CCO 1/8/625]
- Constituency files, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9
  - Area A - London, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/1-43; 1.0 file
    - Battersea North, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/1; 1.0 file
    - Battersea South, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/2; 1.0 file
    - Bermondsey, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/3; 1.0 file
    - Bethnal Green, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/4; 1.0 file
    - Camberwell, Dulwich, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/5; 1.0 file
    - Camberwell, Peckham, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/6; 1.0 file
    - Chelsea, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/7; 1.0 file
    - Cities of London and Westminster, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/8/1; 1.0 file
    - City of London, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/8/2; 1.0 file
    - City of Westminster, Abbey, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/8/3; 1.0 file
    - City of Westminster, St. George's, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/8/4; 1.0 file
    - Deptford, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/9; 1.0 file
    - Fulham East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/10; 1.0 file
    - Fulham West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/11; 1.0 file
    - Greenwich, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/12; 1.0 file
    - Hackney South, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/13; 1.0 file
    - Hammersmith North, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/14; 1.0 file
    - Hammersmith South, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/15; 1.0 file
    - Hampstead, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/16; 1.0 file
    - Holborn and St. Pancras South, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/17; 1.0 file
    - Islington East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/18; 1.0 file
    - Islington North, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/19; 1.0 file
    - Islington South West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/20; 1.0 file
    - Kensington North, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/21; 1.0 file
    - Kensington South, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/22; 1.0 file
    - Lambeth, Brixton, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/23; 1.0 file
    - Lambeth, Norwood, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/24; 1.0 file
    - Lambeth, Vauxhall, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/25; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham North, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/26; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham South, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/27; 1.0 file
    - Lewisham West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/28; 1.0 file
    - Paddington North, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/29; 1.0 file
    - Paddington South, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/30; 1.0 file
    - Poplar, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/31; 1.0 file
    - St. Marylebone, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/32; 1.0 file
    - St. Pancras North, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/33; 1.0 file
    - Shoreditch and Finsbury, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/34; 1.0 file
    - Southwark, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/35; 1.0 file
    - Stepney, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/36; 1.0 file
    - Stoke Newington and Hackney North, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/37; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth Central, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/38; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth, Clapham, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/39; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth, Putney, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/40; 1.0 file
    - Wandsworth, Streatham, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/41; 1.0 file
    - Woolwich East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/42; 1.0 file
    - Woolwich West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/43/1; 1.0 file
    - University of London Graduates' Association, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/43/2; 1.0 file
  - Area B - Northern, Sep 1951-Aug 1953
    CCO 1/9/44-CCO 1/9/77
    - Sep 1951-Aug 1953, CCO 1/9/44; 1.0 file
    - Cumbria, Penrith, and the Border Division, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/45; 1.0 file
    - Cumbria, Whitehaven Division, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/46; 1.0 file
    - Cumbria, Workington, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/47; 1.0 file
    - Darlington, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/48; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/49/50; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/49; 1.0 file
    - Gateshead West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/50; 1.0 file
    - South Shields, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/51; 1.0 file
    - Stockton-on-Tees, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/52; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/53/54; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland North, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/53; 1.0 file
    - Sunderland South, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/54/1; 1.0 file
    - Sep 1951-Aug 1953, 1.0 file
    - Sunderland South, By-Election, Organisation Department file, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/54/3; 1.0 file
    - The Hartlepools, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/55; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Bishop Aukland, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/56; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Blaydon, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/57; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Chester-le-Street, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/58; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Consett, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/59; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Durham, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/60; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Easington, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/61; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Houghton-le-Spring, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/62; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Jarrow, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/63; 1.0 file
    - Durham, North West Durham, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/64; 1.0 file
    - Durham, Sedgefield, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/65; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/66/67; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/66; 1.0 file
    - Middlesborough West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/67; 1.0 file
    - Blyth, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/68; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle Central, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/69; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/70; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle North, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/71; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/72; 1.0 file
    - Tynemouth, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/73; 1.0 file
    - Wallsend, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/74; 1.0 file
    - Berwick on Tweed, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/75; 1.0 file
    - Newcastle, Hexham, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/76; 1.0 file
    - Northumberland, Morpeth, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/77; 1.0 file
  - Area C - North West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953
    CCO 1/9/78-CCO 1/9/157
    - Altrincham and Sale, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/78; 1.0 file
    - Bebington, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/79; 1.0 file
    - Birkenhead, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/80; 1.0 file
    - Stockport, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/81/82; 1.0 file
    - Stockport North, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/81; 1.0 file
    - Stockport South, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/82; 1.0 file
    - Wallasey, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/83; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Cheadle, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/84; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Chester, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/85; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Crewe, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/86; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Knutsford, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/87; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Macclesfield (file A), Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/88/1; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Macclesfield (file B), Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/88/2; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Northwich, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/89; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Runcorn, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/90; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Stalybridge and Hyde, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/91; 1.0 file
    - Cheshire, Wirral, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/92; 1.0 file
    - Accrington (file 1), Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/93; 1.0 file
    - Accrington (file 2), Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/93; 1.0 file
    - Ashton-Under-Lyne, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/94; 1.0 file
    - Barrow-in-Furness, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/95; 1.0 file
    - Blackburn, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/96/97; 1.0 file
    - Blackburn East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/96; 1.0 file
    - Blackburn West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/97; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/98/99; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool North, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/98; 1.0 file
    - Blackpool South, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/99; 1.0 file
    - Bolton, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/100/101; 1.0 file
    - Bolton East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/100; 1.0 file
    - Bolton West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/101; 1.0 file
    - Bootle, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/102; 1.0 file
    - Burnley, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/103; 1.0 file
    - Bury and Radcliffe, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/104; 1.0 file
    - Crosby, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/105; 1.0 file
    - Droylsden, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/106; 1.0 file
    - Eccles, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/107; 1.0 file
    - Leigh, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/108; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/109/117; 1.0 file
    - [Liverpool Edgehill], Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/109
      File missing
    - Liverpool Exchange, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/110; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Garston, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/111; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Kirkdale, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/112; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Scotland, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/113; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Toxteth, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/114; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Walton, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/115; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool Wavertree, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/116; 1.0 file
    - Liverpool West Derby, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/117; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/118/126; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Ardwick, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/118; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Blackley, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/119; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Cheetham, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/120; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Clayton, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/121; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Exchange, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/122; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Gorton, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/123; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Moss Side, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/124; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Withington, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/125; 1.0 file
    - Manchester, Wythenshawe, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/126; 1.0 file
    - Nelson and Colne, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/127; 1.0 file
    - Oldham, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/128/129; 1.0 file
    - Oldham East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/128; 1.0 file
    - Oldham West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/129; 1.0 file
    - Preston, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/130/131; 1.0 file
    - Preston North, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/130; 1.0 file
    - Preston South, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/131; 1.0 file
    - Rochdale, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/132; 1.0 file
    - Rossendale, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/133; 1.0 file
    - St. Helen's, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/134; 1.0 file
    - Salford, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/135/136; 1.0 file
    - Salford East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/135; 1.0 file
    - Salford West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/136; 1.0 file
    - Southport, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/137/1; 1.0 file
    - Southport, By-Election, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/137/2; 1.0 file
    - Southport, By-Election - Miss Dodd's file, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/137/3; 1.0 file
    - Southport, By-Election - Organisation Department file, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/137/4; 1.0 file
    - Stretford, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/138; 1.0 file
    - Warrington, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/139; 1.0 file
    - Wigan, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/140; 1.0 file
    - [Lancashire, Chorley], Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/141
      [File Empty]
    - Lancashire, Clithero, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/142; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Darwen, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/143; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Farnworth, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/144/1; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Farnworth, By-Election (file A), Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/144/2; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Farnworth, By-Election (file B), Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/144/3; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Farnworth, By-Election - Organisation Department file, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/144/4; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Heywood and Royton, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/145; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Huyton, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/146; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Ince, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/147; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Lancaster, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/148; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Middleton and Prestwich, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/149; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Morecombe and Lonsdale, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/150; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Newton, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/151; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, North Fylde, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/152; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Ormskirk, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/153; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, South Fylde, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/154; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Westhoughton, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/155; 1.0 file
    - Lancashire, Widnes, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/156; 1.0 file
    - Westmorland, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/157/1; 1.0 file
    - Combined English Universities Graduates Association, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/157/2; 1.0 file
  - Area D - Yorkshire, Sep 1951-Aug 1953
    CCO 1/9/158-CCO 1/9/213
    - Barnsley, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/158/1; 1.0 file
    - Barnsley, By-Election (file A), Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/158/2; 1.0 file
    - Barnsley, By-Election (file B), Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/158/3; 1.0 file
    - Barnsley, By-Election, G.D.'s file, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/158/4; 1.0 file
    - Mid Yorkshire Federation, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/158/5; 1.0 file
    - Batley and Morley, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/159; 1.0 file
    - Bradford, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/160/163; 1.0 file
    - Bradford Central, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/160; 1.0 file
    - Bradford East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/161; 1.0 file
    - Bradford North, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/162; 1.0 file
    - Bradford South, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/163; 1.0 file
    - Brighouse and Spenborough, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/164; 1.0 file
    - Dewsbury, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/165; 1.0 file
    - Doncaster, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/166; 1.0 file
    - Halifax, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/167; 1.0 file
    - Huddersfield, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/168/169; 1.0 file
    - Huddersfield East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/168; 1.0 file
    - Huddersfield West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/169; 1.0 file
    - Keighley, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/170; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/171/174; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull Central, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/171; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/172; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull Haltemprice, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/173; 1.0 file
    - Kingston-upon-Hull North, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/174; 1.0 file
    - Leeds, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/175/181; 1.0 file
    - Leeds Central, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/175; 1.0 file
    - Leeds North, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/176; 1.0 file
    - Leeds North East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/177; 1.0 file
    - Leeds North West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/178; 1.0 file
    - Leeds South, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/179; 1.0 file
    - Leeds South East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/180/1; 1.0 file
    - Leeds South East, By-Election (file A), Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/180/2; 1.0 file
    - Leeds South East, By-Election (file B), Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/180/3; 1.0 file
    - Leeds South East, By-Election (file C), Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/180/4; 1.0 file
    - Leeds West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/181; 1.0 file
    - Pontefract, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/182; 1.0 file
    - Pudsey, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/183; 1.0 file
    - Rotherham, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/184; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/185/191; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Attercliffe, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/185; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Brightside, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/186; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Hallam, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/187; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Healey, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/188; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Hillsborough, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/189; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield, Neepsend, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/190; 1.0 file
    - Sheffield Park, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/191; 1.0 file
    - Wakefield, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/192; 1.0 file
    - York, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/193; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Barkston Ash, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/194; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Beverley, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/195; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Bridlington, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/196; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Cleveland, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/197/1; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Cleveland, By-Election (file A), Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/197/2; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Cleveland, By-Election (file B), Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/197/3; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Cleveland, By-Election (file C), Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/197/4; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Colne Valley, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/198; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Dearne Valley, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/199; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Don Valley, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/200; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Goole, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/201; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Harrogate, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/202; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Hemsworth, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/203; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Normanton, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/204; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Penistone, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/205; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Richmond, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/206; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Rippon, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/207; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Rother Valley, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/208; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Scarborough and Whitby, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/209; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Shipley, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/210; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Skipton, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/211; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Sowerby, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/212; 1.0 file
    - Yorkshire, Thirsk and Malton, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/213; 1.0 file
  - Area E - East Midlands, Sep 1951-Aug 1953
    CCO 1/9/214-CCO 1/9/255
    - Chesterfield, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/214; 1.0 file
    - Derby, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/215/216; 1.0 file
    - Derby North, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/215; 1.0 file
    - Derby South, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/216; 1.0 file
    - Derbyshire, Belper, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/217; 1.0 file
    - Derbyshire, Bolsover, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/218; 1.0 file
    - Derbyshire, High Peak, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/219; 1.0 file
    - Derbyshire, Ilkeston, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/220; 1.0 file
    - Derbyshire, North East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/221; 1.0 file
    - Derbyshire, South East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/222; 1.0 file
    - Derbyshire, West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/223; 1.0 file
    - Leicester, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/224/227; 1.0 file
    - Leicester North East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/224; 1.0 file
    - Leicester North West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/225; 1.0 file
    - Leicester South East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/226; 1.0 file
    - Leicester South West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/227; 1.0 file
    - Leicestershire, Bosworth, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/228; 1.0 file
    - Leicestershire, Harborough, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/229; 1.0 file
    - Leicestershire, Loughborough, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/230; 1.0 file
    - Leicestershire, Melton, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/231; 1.0 file
    - Grimsby, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/232; 1.0 file
    - Lincoln, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/233; 1.0 file
    - Lincolnshire, Brig, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/234; 1.0 file
    - Lincolnshire, Gainsborough, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/235; 1.0 file
    - Lincolnshire, Grantham, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/236/1; 1.0 file
    - Lincolnshire, Grantham, By-Election - G.D.'s file, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/236/2; 1.0 file
    - Lincolnshire, Grantham, By-Election - Organisation Department file, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/236/3; 1.0 file
    - Lincolnshire, Holland with Boston, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/237; 1.0 file
    - Lincolnshire, Horncastle, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/238; 1.0 file
    - Lincolnshire, Louth, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/239; 1.0 file
    - Lincolnshire, Rutland and Stamford, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/240; 1.0 file
    - Northampton, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/241; 1.0 file
    - Northants., Kettering, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/242; 1.0 file
    - Northants., Peterborough, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/243; 1.0 file
    - Northants., South, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/244; 1.0 file
    - Northants., Wellingborough, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/245; 1.0 file
    - Nottingham, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/246/249; 1.0 file
    - Nottingham Central, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/246; 1.0 file
    - Nottingham East, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/247; 1.0 file
    - Nottingham North West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/248; 1.0 file
    - Nottingham South, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/249; 1.0 file
    - Nottinghamshire, Bassetlaw, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/250; 1.0 file
    - Nottinghamshire, Broxtowe, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/251; 1.0 file
    - Nottinghamshire, Carlton, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/252; 1.0 file
    - Nottinghamshire, Mansfield, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/253; 1.0 file
    - Nottinghamshire, Newark, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/254; 1.0 file
    - Nottinghamshire, Rushcliffe, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/255; 1.0 file
  - Area F- West Midlands, Sep 1951-Aug 1953
    CCO 1/9/256-CCO 1/9/313
    - Cheltenham, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/256; 1.0 file
    - Gloucester, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/257; 1.0 file
    - Gloucestershire, Cirencester and Tewksbury, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/258; 1.0 file
    - Gloucestershire, South, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/259; 1.0 file
    - Gloucestershire, Stroud and Thornbury, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/260; 1.0 file
    - Gloucestershire, West, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/261; 1.0 file
    - Herefordshire, Hereford, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/262; 1.0 file
    - Herefordshire, Leominster, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/263; 1.0 file
    - Shropshire, Ludlow, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/264; 1.0 file
    - Shropshire, Oswestry, Sep 1951-Aug 1953; CCO 1/9/265; 1.0 file